ladder.io 2018-09-07

# Ladder.io - Privacy

Ladder Digital Limited (“us”, “we”, “our”, “Company”) operates the https://ladder.io website (the “Service”).

Your privacy is very important to us. This page informs you of our policies regarding the collection, storage, use, disclosure, and deletion of Personal Information when you use our Service. It also explains how our website uses cookies. Our aim is to bring understanding and clarity on how personal data is processed at Ladder Digital Limited.

We will not use or share your information with anyone except as described in this Privacy Policy.

We use your Personal Information for providing and improving the Service. By using the Service, you agree to the collection and use of information in accordance with this policy. Unless otherwise defined in this Privacy Policy, terms used in this Privacy Policy have the same meanings as in our Terms and Conditions, accessible at https://ladder.io/terms.

We collect “Non-Personal Information” and “Personal Information.” Non-Personal Information includes information that cannot be used to personally identify you, such as anonymous usage data, general demographic information we may collect, referring/exit pages and URLs, platform types, preferences you submit and preferences that are generated based on the data you submit and number of clicks. Personal Information includes only your email and name, which you submit to us through the registration process at the Site.

## 1\. Information collected via Technology.

  1. ### The Service contact form

    1. **The contact form is a basic way of communication with our specialists.** You can find it in many different places at the site, but its construction is always the same. The contact form allows you to send an inquiry about our services, costs estimates or product demos.

    2. **To activate the Service you do not need to submit any Personal Information other than your email address.** To use the Service thereafter, you do not need to submit further Personal Information.

For a better understanding of the inquiry, we additionally ask to choose from the list following information: Business Model, Growth Goals, Marketing Budget, Monthly Revenue. This data is used to answer your inquiry and provide you our products and services.

The data is collected and processed only upon your consent. Your personal data will be stored in our potential clients database for indefinite period of time.

    3. **Your data will be processed until you inform us about your withdraw.** You can withdraw your consent at any time by sending us a message to hello@ladder.io. After that, your data will be erased from our database.

  2. ### Publications & Newsletter

    1. **We share our business strategy knowledge and experience in marketing materials** like: publications (reports, ebooks, guides, checklists, templates, and widgets), blog posts and news. You can find them on our blog and dedicated sites. You can download them, free of charge, at the time that suits you best.

By downloading the publication you are granted a permission to temporarily download one copy of the materials for personal, non-commercial transitory viewing only.

This is the grant of a license, not a transfer of title, and under this license you may not: modify or copy the materials; use the materials for any commercial purpose, or for any public display (commercial or non-commercial); attempt to decompile or reverse engineer any software contained on ladder.io’s web site; remove any copyright or other proprietary notations from the materials; or transfer the materials to another person or “mirror” the materials on any other server. This license shall automatically terminate if you violate any of these restrictions and may be terminated by ladder.io at any time. Upon terminating your viewing of these materials or upon the termination of this license, you must destroy any downloaded materials in your possession whether in electronic or printed format.

 _Our newsletter is a special selection of our freshest blog posts, publications, case studies, events, products_ and _services, as well as the marketing trends, tools and news dedicated to business growth._

The newsletter is designed to share knowledge with marketing specialists (business owners, managers, marketers, CMOs, and engineers).

 **Signing up for the newsletter is voluntary** and can be done at ladder.io and at Ladder Blog. The newsletter is sent to your email periodically (usually once a week) and on special occasions (like publication premiere).

    2. **For the purpose of sharing our marketing materials, we collect following data: name, email address.** This data helps us to understand better our audience.

The data is collected and processed only upon your consent. Your personal data will be stored in our database for the indefinite period of time.

    3. **Your data will be processed until you inform us about your withdraw.** You can withdraw your consent at any time by sending us a message to hello@ladder.io or by an unsubscribing link in the email. After that, your data will be erased from our database.

  3. ### Cookies & Pixel Tags

    1. In an effort to improve the quality of the Service, we track information provided to us by your browser or by our software application when you view or use the Service, such as the website you came from (known as the “referring URL”), the type of browser you use, the device from which you connected to the Service, the time and date of access, and other information that does not personally identify you. We track this information using cookies, or small text files (pixel tags) which include an anonymous unique identifier. Cookies are sent to a user’s browser from our servers and are stored on the user’s computer hard drive. Sending a cookie to a user’s browser enables us to collect Non-Personal information about that user and keep a record of the user’s preferences when utilizing our services, both on an individual and aggregate basis. For example, the Company may use cookies to collect the following information: location, anonymized IP address, website activity.

    2. **The Company may use both persistent and session cookies** ; persistent cookies remain on your computer after you close your session and until you delete them, while session cookies expire when you close your browser.

    3. **We also may receive reports based on the use of these technologies by our service/analytics providers** (like Google Analytics). We use those reports to obtain statistics about traffic and site interaction, so that we can improve our website and your experience.

 _We do not link the information we store in cookies to any personal data you submit on our site._

## 2\. Information you provide us by registering for an account.

In addition to the information provided automatically by your browser when you visit the Site, to become an account holder to the Service you will need to create a personal profile. You can create a profile by registering with the Service and entering your email address, and creating a user name and a password. _By registering, you are authorizing us to collect, store and use your email address in accordance with this Privacy Policy._

## Personal information:

Except as otherwise stated in this Privacy Policy, we do not sell, trade, rent or otherwise share for marketing purposes your Personal Information with third parties without your consent. We do share Personal Information with vendors who are performing services for the Company, such as the servers for our email communications who are provided access to user’s email address for purposes of sending emails from us. Those vendors use your Personal Information only at our direction and in accordance with our Privacy Policy.

**In general, the Personal Information you provide to us is used to help us communicate with you.** For example, we use Personal Information to contact users in response to questions, solicit feedback from users, provide technical support, and inform users about promotional offers.

## Non-personal information:

**In general, we use Non-Personal Information to help us improve the Service and customize the user experience.** We also aggregate Non-Personal Information in order to track trends and analyze use patterns on the Site. This Privacy Policy does not limit in any way our use or disclosure of Non-Personal Information and we reserve the right to use and disclose such Non-Personal Information to our partners, advertisers and other third parties at our discretion.

In the event we undergo a business transaction such as a merger, acquisition by another company, or sale of all or a portion of our assets, your Personal Information may be among the assets transferred. You acknowledge and consent that such transfers may occur and are permitted by this Privacy Policy, and that any acquirer of our assets may continue to process your Personal Information as set forth in this Privacy Policy. If our information practices change at any time in the future, we will post the policy changes to the Site so that you may opt out of the new information practices. We suggest that you check the Site periodically if you are concerned about how your information is used.

## For the purpose of functionality:

These cookies, pixel tags and other technologies remember your usage of our website. We use **Intercom** cookies to provide you with an experience more appropriate and to make your use of the Services more tailored.

## For the purpose of analytics:

These cookies, pixel tags and other technologies collect information about way how you interact with our website. We use **Google** **Analytics** , **Hubspot** , **FullStory** , and **Hotjar** cookies to understand how you arrive at and browse our products and website to identify areas for improvement such as navigation, user experience, and marketing campaigns.

## For the purpose of advertising and retargeting:

These cookies, pixel tags and other technologies collect information about your browsing habits in order to make advertising relevant to you and your interests. They remember the websites you have visited and that information is shared with other parties such as advertising technology service providers and advertisers. We use **Facebook** **Pixel** , **LinkedIn Insights** , **Twitter Pixel** , **Quora Pixel** , **Taboola Pixel** , **Sumome tag** , **Bing cookies** , and **Google AdWords cookies**.

## For the purpose of social media sharing:

These cookies, pixel tags and other technologies are used when you share information using a social media sharing button. The social network will record that you have done this. This information may be linked to targeting/advertising activities.

## How to manage cookies:

You can deactivate cookies through a functionality built into your web browser. Browser manufacturers provide help pages relating to cookie management in their products. Please see below to learn more about how to control cookie settings through your browser:

[Google Chrome](https://support.google.com/chrome/answer/95647);

[Mozilla Firefox](https://support.mozilla.org/en-US/kb/enable-and-disable-cookies-website-preferences);

[Microsoft Edge](https://privacy.microsoft.com/en-us/windows-10-microsoft-edge-and-privacy);

[Microsoft Internet Explorer](https://support.microsoft.com/pl-pl/help/17442/windows-internet-explorer-delete-manage-cookies);

[Safari](https://support.apple.com/kb/ph21411).

Certain third-party advertising networks permit users to opt out of or customize preferences associated with your Internet browsing. [Click here](https://adssettings.google.com/) to customize Google cookies preferences. You can opt out of interest-based targeting provided by participating ad servers through the [Digital Advertising Alliance](http://youradchoices.com/).

_If you do not accept cookies you may not be able to use all aspects of our website. You will not be able to opt-out of any cookies or other technologies that are “strictly necessary” for the Services._

**We implement security measures designed to protect your information from unauthorized access.** Your account is protected by your account password and we urge you to take steps to keep your personal information safe by not disclosing your password and by logging out of your account after each use. We further protect your information from potential security breaches by implementing certain technological security measures including encryption, firewalls and secure socket layer technology. However, these measures do not guarantee that your information will not be accessed, disclosed, altered or destroyed by breach of such firewalls and secure server software. _By using our Service, you acknowledge that you understand and agree to assume these risks._

We use third-party vendors and hosting partners, for hardware, software, networking, storage, and related technology we need to run ladder.io. Your personal data is stored in secured networks accessible by a limited number of persons who have special access rights to these systems.

## Regarding Third-Party Software:

We occasionally work with third parties who support us with services: **Google Analytics** and **FullStory** tracking technologies, **Facebook** , **LinkedIn** and **Twitter** audience tools, **HubSpot** , **MailChimp** , **Unbounce** , **Slack** and **Intercom** communication tools. Those third parties might need to access to specific information to carry out their work for us. We rigorously vet these third-party vendors to ensure they meet our privacy standards and limit the data they can access to only what is necessary for them to perform their contracted tasks.

**You have the right at any time to prevent us from contacting you for marketing purposes.** When we send a promotional communication to a user, the user can opt out of further promotional communications by following the unsubscribe instructions provided in each promotional email. You can also indicate that you do not wish to receive marketing communications from us in the footer section of any email we send. Please note that notwithstanding the promotional preferences you indicate by either unsubscribing or opting out in the Settings section of the Site, we may continue to send you administrative emails including, for example, periodic updates to our Privacy Policy.

Additionally, at this time you have the right to request from us:

  1. access to your personal data;

  2. correction of your personal data;

  3. erasure of your personal data;

  4. restriction of processing;

  5. data portability.

_To perform any of your rights please email us at hello@ladder.io_

Your request will be resolved in a timely and effective manner. We might contact you to arrange details of your request.

As part of the Service, we may provide links to or compatibility with other websites or applications. However, we are not responsible for the privacy practices employed by those websites or the information or content they contain. This Privacy Policy applies solely to information collected by us through the Site and the Service. Therefore, this Privacy Policy does not apply to your use of a third party website accessed by selecting a link on our Site or via our Service. To the extent that you access or use the Service through or on another website or application, then the privacy policy of that other website or application will apply to your access or use of that site or application. We encourage our users to read the privacy statements of other websites before proceeding to use them.

The Company reserves the right to change this policy and our Terms of Service at any time. We will notify you of significant changes to our Privacy Policy by sending a notice to the primary email address specified in your account or by placing a prominent notice on our site. Significant changes will go into effect 30 days following such notification. Non-material changes or clarifications will take effect immediately. You should periodically check the Site and this privacy page for updates.

If you have any questions regarding this Privacy Policy or the practices of this Site, please contact us by sending an email to hello@ladder.io.

_Last Updated: This Privacy Policy was last updated on 5/23/2018._
